hispanicallyspeakingnews.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | HispanicallySpeakingNews.com

At [http://www.HS-News.com](http://www.hs-news.com/) we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our web site and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. The policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy. 

You may provide personal information to [http://www.HS-News.com](http://www.hs-news.com/)  in one of three ways: (1) by sharing your e-mail address and subscribing to email newsletters or requesting site updates, (2) by sharing personal information when you provide tips to our news department, (3) by sharing personal information when you post comments on our posts or stories. We may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain complete access to our site.

In addition to personal information—such as name, street, zip code, and e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers—we may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the operating system you are working on, the internet browser you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, and the web sites you visit directly before and after your visit to [http://www.HS-News.com](http://www.hs-news.com/). 

The more we know about you, the better we are able to customize our web site to suit your personal preferences and interests. The e-mail address you provide may be used by Hispanically Speaking News for any reason, such as contacting you for editorial purposes or to advise you of any changes to our site. We may also from time to time send you messages about our marketing partners’ products.   
To maintain a site that is free of charge and does not require registration, we display advertisements on our web site. We also use the information you give us to help our advertisers target the audience they want to reach. At no time does any party other than Hispanically Speaking News have access to your personally identifiable information, and you will never be contacted by any party other than Hispanically Speaking News. The only exceptions to the foregoing are that we may disclose personally identifiable information (i) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, (ii) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take actions regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of another person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, or (iii) in the event we are acquired by or merged with another company. 

Non-personally identifiable information (such as stated above) may be shared in aggregate form with our advertisers or marketing partners but your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed to them. 

We have also contracted with a number of advertising network partners to monitor certain pages of our website and RSS feeds for the purpose of reporting website and RSS traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, these advertising network partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to these network partners. And Google’s privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

Third parties and web sites that have links on our site may also collect or use information about you. The information practices of other companies or people that Hispanically Speaking News does not employ or manage are not covered by this privacy statement. 

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

* * *

We never censor comments based on political or ideological point of view. We only delete those comments that are abusive, off-topic, use excessive foul language, or include ad hominem attacks. We pre-moderate comments on our blog posts and post-moderate comments on news stories.

##### Frequently Asked Questions

**Q:** I posted a comment. Why can’t I see it on the site?  
**A:** The volume of comments on the site has grown rapidly, and sometimes our moderators have trouble approving the comments fast enough.

**Q:** Why am I blocked from commenting on Hispanically Speaking News?  
**A:** There are a few scenarios in which a comment might be blocked: 

  * A comment is abusive, off-topic, uses excessive foul language, or includes an ad hominem attack
  * If a commenter has previously posted comments that are abusive, off-topic, used excessive foul language, or include ad hominem attacks, a moderator may decide to ban the commenter’s IP address. This means the abusive commenter is banned from commenting on the site in the future, even if the later comments are not abusive. We ban IPs because the sheer volume of comments makes it too time consuming to individually delete comments written by someone with a pattern of abuse.
  * If a commenter shares a computer or IP address with someone who has written abusive comments, it could result in a comment being blocked even if the commenter has never posted anything abusive.
